(Howard:)Did you hear about the
accident at the bio lab?
(Leonard:)No.
What happened?
(Howard:)They were injecting rats
with radioactive isotopes
(Howard:)and one of the techs got bit.
(Raj:)Did he get superpowers?
(Howard:)No, he got five stitches
and a tetanus shot.
(Raj:)Oh. Well, that's disappointing.
(Howard:)Why?
(Raj:)Well, you get bit by a
radioactive animal in a lab,
(Raj:)you kind of want to turn
into a superhero.
(Howard:)Yeah, but who'd want
to become Rat-Man?
(Raj:)Who wouldn't?
(Raj:)You could zip through
a maze in nothing flat,
(Raj:)squeeze through
really small holes,
(Raj:)and shut down restaurants
in a single bound.
(Raj:)And the best part is,
if I were Rat-Man,
(Raj:)you could be my
sidekick, Mouse Boy.
(Howard:)Mouse Boy?
You don't like "Mouse Boy"?
How about "Kid Vermin"?
(Howard:)First of all,
if we had superpowers,